SATRIA RAHMAT MUSYARIFIN BACKEND & AUTOMATION DEVELOPER

South Jakarta, Indonesia | +62 81251389915 | sumgmng@gmail.com | Linkedin | Github

PROFILE

Experienced backend and automation developer with 3 years of work experience focused on efficiency and security. As a developer, I am open to work in backend and automation environments or even cybersecurity with various skills that I have learned in the description below.

SKILLS

- Backend Developer
- Automation/Scraping

- Reverse Engineering
- Cyber Security

TOOLS

- Python
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- PHP NativeJava Native
- Golang Native
- Express Js
- Flask
- Django
- MongoDB
- SQL
- CSS
- BeautifulSoup
- Requests Html

- Selenium
- Undetected ChromeDriver
- Puppeteer
- WhiskeyScoket
- WhiskeySPandas
- Git
- Linux
- Threading

- PyTelegramBotAPI
- Docker
- Jadx
- Adb
- Frida
- Burpsuite
- Paramiko
- Postman
 Hoppscotch

- **LANGUAGE**
 - Indonesia (Native)
 - English (Beginner)

WORK EXPERIENCE

South Jakarta January 2021 – Present

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (Automation Focused) – FREELANCE

- Create <u>Captcha solver</u>
- Automate serve customers on <u>itemku</u>
- Create a Zalora scraper tool for getting product's detail
- Create <u>Apx</u> The wrapper and helper for Flask
- Automate VM management on IdCloudHost
- Create an article scraper tool
- Automate mirroring data from <u>p-store</u> to personal website
- Create scraper tools for Ruangguru, flightradar24, Mapclub, and Foot Locker
- Create Money app farming bot
- Automate post data on <u>asuransi.partaiperindo.com</u>
- Create <u>Indosat Simpel</u> automate transaction as extension of <u>TigaPutri</u>
- Automate tiktok interaction
- Create Gojek account generator
- Create <u>Plagiarism Scanner</u> web based
- Automate Checkout product on BliBli and JDID
- Create Whatsapp blaster and scrapper
- Create Sociolla scrapper
- Automate transaction on telegram bot
- Create Live streaming cloner

• Automate <u>audiomack</u> interaction

South Jakarta

AUTOMATION DEVELOPER – AUTOBOT KARYA INDONESIA – FREELANCE REMOTE

July 2021 – August 2022

- Automate submit and collect covid vaccine data on pedulilindungi.id
- Create an unofficial WhatsApp API for sending messages.
- Create an API to generate and manage license key autobot products.
- Optimizing speed in the scraping process

South Jakarta

May 2022 – July 2023

BACKEND DEVELOPER - ONTIME TECHNOLOGY INDONESIA - FULL TIME ONSITE

- Create a scheduler for data manipulation and sending email
- Create API (Dajngo Based) and mongodb queries to get data that is easy to consume
- Create microservice using rust language
- Optimization of the code on the API and Library
- Create some scraper tools

•

South Tangerang

May 2023 – December 2023

BACKEND DEVELOPER - SIBER FORENSIK INDONESIA - FULL TIME ONSITE

- Create a scheduler for data manipulation and sending email
- Create API (Daingo Based) and mongodb queries to get data that is easy to consume
- Create microservice using rust language
- Optimization of the code on the API and Library
- Create some scraper tools

South Jakarta

October 2023 - Present

BACKEND DEVELOPER – META PESONA TEKNOLOGI INDONESIA – FULL TIME REMOTE

- Build scalable architecture for API using Django
- Create Django wrapper for handling and logging error
- Rendering email template and integrate to SMTP Server
- Optimization of the code on the API and Library

PROJECTS

Some automation project demonstrations can be seen through the following url https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLUR--SLLapFskSFQ5- vRjbJmoDYbw9v6

EDUCATION

SYARIF HIDAYATULLAH VOCATIONAL SCHOOL

Department of Computer and Network Engineering

Muara Badak, East Kalimantan August 2019 – Apr 2022

- Create web-based applications for grouping reading interests using Flask and Scikit-learn.
- Build a local network circuit using mikrotik.
- Automate networking via telegram using paramiko and pyTelegramBotAPI.

COURSE

- Python Sololearn
- <u>JavaScript</u> Sololearn
- PHP Sololearn
- <u>SQL</u> Sololearn
- GO Sololearn